Hi, my name is Regent Tolentino. You can call me John.
I'm 24 years old. I have a three year work experience with
the BPO industry doing inbound and outbound
calling. First, I served as a technical
consultant, wherein my multitasking skills has been definitely
enhanced. Then eventually I switched to customer service,
wherein our integrity plays a very big role.
Definitely, sales must always be on point, ahead of the target,
and at the same time making sure that each and every customer
will always be satisfied with my assistance.
And on top of all these skills, I also have a talent with
doing graphic designs, creating flyers, business cards,
and social media advertisements, which will really be
helpful for clients marketing needs.
And I can assure you that I'm not just going to be another number
on your payroll, but definitely a good addition to your company.
Once again, this is Regent Tolentino. Thank you
and goodbye.